<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fractal Lotus on obxium</title>
    <link>https://obxium.com/fractal-lotus/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fractal Lotus on obxium</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2020 17:07:21 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://obxium.com/fractal-lotus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>FRACTAL LOTUS 1</title>
      <link>https://obxium.com/fractal-lotus/fractal-lotus-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2020 17:07:21 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://obxium.com/fractal-lotus/fractal-lotus-1/</guid>
      <description>FRACTAL LOTUS 1 is a complete cryptoart experience featuring the beauty of a lotus flower combined with the infinite worlds of artificial intelligence. About FRACTAL LOTUS 1 The artwork owner receives a Kusama RMRK token, with links to the original PNG art on IPFS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FRACTAL LOTUS 2</title>
      <link>https://obxium.com/fractal-lotus/fractal-lotus-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2020 17:07:21 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://obxium.com/fractal-lotus/fractal-lotus-2/</guid>
      <description>FRACTAL LOTUS 2 is a complete cryptoart experience featuring the beauty of a lotus flower combined with the infinite worlds of artificial intelligence. About FRACTAL LOTUS 2 The artwork owner receives a Kusama RMRK token, with links to the original PNG art on IPFS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FRACTAL LOTUS 3</title>
      <link>https://obxium.com/fractal-lotus/fractal-lotus-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2020 17:07:21 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://obxium.com/fractal-lotus/fractal-lotus-3/</guid>
      <description>FRACTAL LOTUS 3 is a complete cryptoart experience featuring the beauty of a lotus flower combined with the infinite worlds of artificial intelligence. About FRACTAL LOTUS 3 The artwork owner receives a Kusama RMRK token, with links to the original PNG art on IPFS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FRACTAL LOTUS 4</title>
      <link>https://obxium.com/fractal-lotus/fractal-lotus-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2020 17:07:21 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://obxium.com/fractal-lotus/fractal-lotus-4/</guid>
      <description>FRACTAL LOTUS 4 is a complete cryptoart experience featuring the beauty of a lotus flower combined with the infinite worlds of artificial intelligence. About FRACTAL LOTUS 4 The artwork owner receives a Kusama RMRK token, with links to the original PNG art on IPFS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FRACTAL LOTUS 5</title>
      <link>https://obxium.com/fractal-lotus/fractal-lotus-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2020 17:07:21 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://obxium.com/fractal-lotus/fractal-lotus-5/</guid>
      <description>FRACTAL LOTUS 5 is a complete cryptoart experience featuring the beauty of a lotus flower combined with the infinite worlds of artificial intelligence. About FRACTAL LOTUS 5 The artwork owner receives a Kusama RMRK token, with links to the original PNG art on IPFS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FRACTAL LOTUS 6</title>
      <link>https://obxium.com/fractal-lotus/fractal-lotus-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2020 17:07:21 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://obxium.com/fractal-lotus/fractal-lotus-6/</guid>
      <description>FRACTAL LOTUS 6 is a complete cryptoart experience featuring the beauty of a lotus flower combined with the infinite worlds of artificial intelligence. About FRACTAL LOTUS 6 The artwork owner receives a Kusama RMRK token, with links to the original PNG art on IPFS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FRACTAL LOTUS 7</title>
      <link>https://obxium.com/fractal-lotus/fractal-lotus-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2020 17:07:21 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://obxium.com/fractal-lotus/fractal-lotus-7/</guid>
      <description>FRACTAL LOTUS 7 is a complete cryptoart experience featuring the beauty of a lotus flower combined with the infinite worlds of artificial intelligence. About FRACTAL LOTUS 7 The artwork owner receives a Kusama RMRK token, with links to the original PNG art on IPFS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FRACTAL LOTUS 8</title>
      <link>https://obxium.com/fractal-lotus/fractal-lotus-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2020 17:07:21 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://obxium.com/fractal-lotus/fractal-lotus-8/</guid>
      <description>FRACTAL LOTUS 8 is a complete cryptoart experience featuring the beauty of a lotus flower combined with the infinite worlds of artificial intelligence. About FRACTAL LOTUS 8 The artwork owner receives a Kusama RMRK token, with links to the original PNG art on IPFS.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
